Oh, he's LeBron James
He's the best in the world on and off of the court
And I can't but to glaze
No, I can't help but to glaze when I hear his name
What a beautiful finals
What a beautiful finals when the Lakers win the playoffs (best in the NBA)
The NBA, yeah he's the one they call LeBron
LeBron James is the name that everybody has heard of
Better than Michael Jordan
'Cause MJ never had this kind of glaze
But ts not glaze 'cause it's LeBron, oh
LeBron James, the name that everyone has heard of
Better than Michael Jordan
'Cause MJ never had this kind of glaze
We all love LeBron
It's a fact
I mean look at it this way oh, I mean technically the Lakers are saved
Well, this calls for a toast so, pour the champagne
Oh, it's a fact
I mean look at it this way oh, I mean technically the Lakers are saved
Well, this calls for a toast so, pour the champagne
Pour the champagne
LeBron James is the name that everybody has heard of
Better than Michael Jordan
'Cause MJ never had this kind of glaze
But ts not glaze 'cause it's LeBron, oh
LeBron James, the name that everyone has heard of
Better than Michael Jordan
'Cause MJ never had this kind of glaze
We all love LeBron
He's my glorious king